If you want to edit one of your projects in general,
you must first select the package you want to modify.
The selected package becomes highlighted
and its contents are displayed on the right side.
Use the "Edit project" button located on the right to start your editing process.
If you want to upload your data to a specific folder,
you must first select that folder.
You can add your data in two ways, using either "File Upload" or "Import".
The "File Upload", allows you to add data from a local storage,
such as your computer.
To use the file upload, make sure that the "File Upload" tab is selected
and click on the plus symbol.
A file explorer will open in a new window
where you can select the files you want to upload.
Once you have selected the files, click "Open"
and your selected files will appear in the FDOrganizer.
In case you have added a file by mistake,
you can easily delete it by using the recycle bin.
To finally upload your data to the FDOrganizer, start the upload process
by clicking on the "Start Upload" button on the bottom right.
A pop-up window will appear where you can either cancel
or confirm the upload process.
If you choose "Abort" the file upload will stop
and you can continue with the selection of the data.
If you choose "Yes" your files will be uploaded to your package.
Of course, if necessary, you can also delete your files after they have been uploaded.
Just use the recycle bin.
When you click on the symbol, a dialogue box will offer you two options.
You can either keep your file by selecting "Do not delete"
or permanently delete it by choosing "Delete file".
Please note that if you delete a file that you have uploaded manually,
you will need to upload it again if you want to recover it.